Wallen, Saul Papers 5012
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Labor Standard Assn., 4/17/53 - ElleBaron Foundary Co., 6/13/55 (Box 120)
  - Landers Plastics Inc. and Direct Affil. Local 24904 L-45261, 1965 (Box 120, Folder 12)
  - Latrobe Steel Co. Latrobe Penn. -and- U.S.W.A. Gr No. W-127, 1964 (Box 120, Folder 13)
  - Latrobe Steel Co. Latrobe Penn. -and- U.S.W.A. Gr. No. W-130, 1964 (Box 120, Folder 14)
  - Latrobe Steel Co. Latrobe Penn. -and- U.S.W.A. Gr. No. W-131, 1964 (Box 120, Folder 15)
  - Latrobe Steel Co. Latrobe Penn. -and- U.S.W.A. Gr. Nos. 79, 90, 1964 (Box 120, Folder 16)
  - Latrobe Steel Co. Latrobe Penn. -and- U.S.W.A. W-143, 1964 (Box 120, Folder 17)
  - A.C. Lawrence Leather Company -and- A.C. Lawrence Leather Workers' Union - Winchester N.H., 1950 (Box 120, Folder 18)
  - A.C. Lawrence Leather Co. (and) A.C. Lawrence Leather Workers Union Local 2, 1956 (Box 120, Folder 19)
  - Lawrence Tribune and Lawrence Typographical Union, 1965 (Box 120, Folder 20)
  - Leach - Heckel Company Case #2 SW, 1946 (Box 120, Folder 21)
  - Leach Heckel Leather Company Salem, Massachusetts and I.F.L.W.U. Local 21, 1946 (Box 120, Folder 22)
  - Leach - Heckel, Inc. and International Fur and Leather Workers Union Local 21, 1949 (Box 120, Folder 23)
  - Leach - Heckel, Inc. and International Fur and Leather Workers Union Local 21, 1950 (Box 120, Folder 24)
  - Leach - Heckel, Inc. and International Fur and Leather Workers Union CIO, 1950 (Box 120, Folder 25)
  - Leach Heckel Leather Co., Salem and Int'l Fur and Leather Workers Local 21, 1950 (Box 120, Folder 26)
  - Leach - Heckel, Inc. and International Fur and Leather Workers Union CIO, 1951 (Box 120, Folder 27)
  - Leach - Heckel, Inc. and International Fur and Leather Workers Union Local 21, 1952 (Box 120, Folder 28)
  - Leach - Heckel, Inc. and International Fur and Leather Workers Union Local 21, 1952 (Box 120, Folder 29)
  - Leach - Heckel, Inc. and International Fur and Leather Workers Union Local 21, 1954 (Box 120, Folder 30)
  - Leach - Heckel, Inc. and International Fur and Leather Workers Union Local 21, 1954 (Box 120, Folder 31)
  - Leach - Heckel, Inc. and International Fur and Leather Workers Union Local 21, 1954 (Box 120, Folder 32)
  - Leach - Heckel, Inc. and International Fur and Leather Workers Union Local 21, 1954 (Box 120, Folder 33)
  - Leach - Heckel, Inc. and International Fur and Leather Workers Union Local 21, 1954 (Box 120, Folder 34)
  - Leach - Heckel, Inc. and International Fur and Leather Workers Union Local 21, 1954 (Box 120, Folder 35)
  - Leach - Heckel, Inc. and International Fur and Leather Workers Union Local 21, 1961 (Box 120, Folder 36)
  - Leach-Heckel Leather Co. -and- Leather Workers International Union, 1964 (Box 120, Folder 37)
  - Lebanon Knitting Mills And International Ladies' Garment Workers Local 232-324 L-204-63, 1963 (Box 120, Folder 38)
  - E.L. Lebaron Foundry Company -and- International Molders and Foundry Workers of N. America Local 399 Brockton, 1955 (Box 120, Folder 39)
- Lee Rubber and Tire Co., 7/9/59 - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1/9/61 (Box 121)
  - Lee Tire and Rubber Corpn. Conshohocken, Penn. URCL and PWA Local 227 Case L-24338 Phi. L-166-59, 1959 (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - Lee Rubber and Tire Co. and URCL and PWA Local 227 Case L, 1960 (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Lee Tire and Rubber Co. Conshohocken, Penn. (and) URCL and PWA Local 227, 1960 (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Lee Tire and Rubber Corpn. Conshohocken, Penn. (and) URCL and PWA Local 227, 1960 (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Lee Tire and Rubber Co. and URCL and PWA Case No. L 29495 Phi. L-603-60, 1961 (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - Leominster Manufacturers' Association and United Novelty Celluloid Workers. Local 61, 1946 (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - Lever Brothers Co. Cambridge, Mass. (and) International Chemical Workers Union, 1955 (Box 121, Folder 7)
  - G. Levor and Co. and Amalg. Meat Cutters #41, 1967 (Box 121, Folder 8)
  - E. Frank Lewis Company and United Textile Workers of America-AFL, 1948 (Box 121, Folder 9)
  - Lewis-Shepard Co. Watertown, Mass. (and) United Steelworkers of America, 1958 (Box 121, Folder 10)
  - Lewis-Shepard Company and U.S.W.A., 1964 (Box 121, Folder 11)
  - Lewiston Gas Light Co. Lewiston, Maine (and) UMWA, Region 5 14 Lisbon St. Lewiston, Me., 1956 (Box 121, Folder 12)
  - Lewiston Gas Light Co. Lewiston, Maine (and) United Mine Workers of America, 1956 (Box 121, Folder 13)
  - Locke-Devere Div. Locke Mfg. Companies, Inc. and I.U.E. Local 228 L-47675, 1965 (Box 121, Folder 14)
  - The Lock Steel Chain Co. Bridgeport, Conn. (and) Local 228 - I.U.E. Case L-24221 L-45-59, 1959 (Box 121, Folder 15)
  - Longshoremen and Associated Occupations 8-18-48 and 10-21-48, 1948 (Box 121, Folder 16)
  - Loring Leather Company and International Fur and Leather Workers Union-Local 21, 1948 (Box 121, Folder 17)
  - Lorraine Manufacturing Co. -and- Textile Workers Union of America, CIO, 1949 (Box 121, Folder 18)
  - Lowell Currier Citizen and Electro-Typers Union, 1963 (Box 121, Folder 19)
  - C.A. Lund and Co. United Steelworkers of Amer., CIO Local 4617, 1952 (Box 121, Folder 20)
  - C.A. Lund and Co. and United Steelworkers of Amer., CIO, 1952 (Box 121, Folder 21)
  - C.A. Lund and Company Laconia, New Hampshire (and) United Steelworkers of America Case L-28737 Bos. L-169-60, 1959 (Box 121, Folder 22)
  - Lynn Gas and Electric Company Lynn, Mass. (and) United Gas, Coke and Chemical Workers of America Local 497, 1955 (Box 121, Folder 23)
  - Lynn Gas and Electric Company Lynn, Mass. (and) United Gas, Coke and Chemical Workers, CIO, 1955 (Box 121, Folder 24)
  - M.B. Manufacturing New Haven Conn. -and- United Electric Radio and Machine Workers of America Local 243, 1955 (Box 121, Folder 25)
  - Mack Manufacturing Co. Allentown, Pennsylvania (and) UAW-CIO Joint Pension Bd., 1957-1958 (Box 121, Folder 26)
  - Maj. Furn. Co. and Wood. Spec. Co. of Boston -and- UIU, Allied Furn. Workers, Local 136, 1955 (Box 121, Folder 27)
  - Mack Trucks, 1962 (Box 121, Folder 28)
  - Mack Trucks, Inc. and VAW, 1963 (Box 121, Folder 29)
  - Maine Central R.R. (and) Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, 1960 (Box 121, Folder 30)
  - Mallory Hat Corpn. Canbury, Ct. (and) United Hatters, Cap and Millinery Workers International Union and Locals, 108, 10, 11-12, 1957 (Box 121, Folder 31)
  - Manchester Union Leader Manchester, N.H. Manchester Newspaper build, Local 167, 1962 (Box 121, Folder 32)
  - The Manufacturing Jewelers and International Association of Machinists - Lodge 129, 1949 (Box 121, Folder 33)
  - Malden Knitting Mills and International Ladies Garment Workers, 1948 (Box 121, Folder 34)
  - Malleable Iron Fittings and United Steelworkers of America, 1946 (Box 121, Folder 35)
  - Marinette Paper Co. Fort Edward, N.Y. (and) United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, 1959 (Box 121, Folder 36)
  - Market Forge Company -and- United Steelworkers of America Local 2431, 1951 (Box 121, Folder 37)
  - Market Forge Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1953 (Box 121, Folder 38)
  - Mason Tanning -and- IFLWU, Local 21, 1954 (Box 121, Folder 39)
  - Mason Tanning Company Salem, Mass. (and) Leather Workers Org. Committee, 1951 (Box 121, Folder 40)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology Cambridge, Mass. (and) M.I.T. Employers Unions, 1959 (Box 121, Folder 41)
  - Mass. Institute of Technology Cambridge, Mass. (and) Building Service Employees' International Union, Local 254, 1959 (Box 121, Folder 42)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (and) M.I.T. Employers Union, 1960 (Box 121, Folder 43)
- Massachusetts Leather Mfgs. Assn., 1949 - Metropolitan Transit Authority, 12/31/57 (Box 122)
  - Data - Negotiations of New Contract. Massachusetts Leather Manufacturers' Association and International Fur and Leather Workers Union, 1949 (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Massachusetts Leather Manufacturers Association and Member Firms and International Fur and Leather Workers Union - General Wage Revision, 1950 (Box 122, Folder 2)
    August 3, 1950
  - Massachusetts Leather Manufacturers Association and Member Firms, and International Fur and Leather Workers Union - General Wage Revision (Exhibits and Notes), 1950 (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - Leather Manufacturers Association, 1954 (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Massachusetts Leather Manufacturers, 1962 (Box 122, Folder 5)
    June 11, 1962
  - Masurel Worsted Company, 1954 (Box 122, Folder 6)
    July 2, 1954
  - Matz Tanning Company (Foster Street, Peabody) and Leather Workers International Union, 1956 (Box 122, Folder 7)
    March 13, 1956
  - Matz Tanning Company (Peabody, Massachusetts) and Leather Workers International Union Local 21, 1959 (Box 122, Folder 8)
    December 7, 1959
  - Matz Tanning Company (Peabody, Massachusetts) and Leather Workers International Union Local 21 - Piece Rate for Operator Splitting Machine, 1959 (Box 122, Folder 9)
    December 9, 1959
  - Mats Tanning Company (Peabody, Massachusetts) and Leather Workers International Union Local 21, 1959 (Box 122, Folder 10)
    December 19, 1959
  - Mayhew Steel Products, Incorporated (Shelburne Falls, Massachusetts) and United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America Local 274, 1956 (Box 122, Folder 11)
    October 17, 1956
  - J.H. McNamara Company and International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 379, 1967 (Box 122, Folder 12)
    August 15, 1967
  - Merck and Company Incorporated (Rahway, New Jersey) and Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers Local 13-575, 1957 (Box 122, Folder 13)
    December 13, 1957
  - Massachusetts Leather Manufacturers Association and Leather Workers International Union - Blue Cross Refund Arbitration, 1962 (Box 122, Folder 14)
  - Merit Manufacturing, Incorporated, and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 422, 1953 (Box 122, Folder 15)
    July 31, 1953
  - Merrimack Leather Company and International Fur and Leather Workers Union, 1947 (Box 122, Folder 16)
    March 24, 1947
  - Merrimack Leather Company and International Fur and Leather Workers Union Local 212, 1947 (Box 122, Folder 17)
  - Marrow Machine Company (Hartford, Connecticut) and International Union of Electrical Workers Local 249, 1961 (Box 122, Folder 18)
    October 20, 1961
  - Metropolitan Transit Authority and Local Union 104, 1948 (Box 122, Folder 19)
    August 27, 1948
  - Metropolitan Transit Authority and Division 589 of the Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America, 1957 (Box 122, Folder 20)
    Bound
  - Metropolitan Transit Authority, 1957 (Box 122, Folder 21)
  - Metropolitan Transit Authority, 1957 (Box 122, Folder 22)
  - Metropolitan Transit Authority (Boston, Massachusetts) and Association of Engineers, Architects, and Draftsmen Local 105, 1956 (Box 122, Folder 23)
    December 6, 1956
  - Metropolitan Transit Authority (Boston, Massachusetts) and Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America Division 589, 1957 (Box 122, Folder 24)
    May 29, 1957
  - Metropolitan Transit Authority (Boston, Massachusetts) and Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America Division 589 (Box 122, Folder 25)
- Metropolitan Transit Authority, 1957 - Mobil Oil Co., 11/4/66 (Box 123)
  - Metropolitan Transit Authority -and- Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric and Motor Coach Employees of America, 1957 (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - Metropolitan Transit Authority -and- Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric and Motor Coach Employees of America, 1957 (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - Metropolitan Transit Company, 1959 (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - George J. Meyer Mfg. Co. Worcester Division -and- USWA Local 5641, 1965 (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - Mica Insulator Company Schenectady, N.Y. -and- International Association of Machinists, 1957 (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - Milk Industry, 1956 (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - Miller Electric Co. Woonsocket, R.I. and U.S.W.A., 1967 (Box 123, Folder 7)
  - Millers Falls Company, 1952 (Box 123, Folder 8)
  - Millers Falls Company, 1952 (Box 123, Folder 9)
  - Millers Falls Company, 1953 (Box 123, Folder 10)
  - The Minot Wood Heel Company -and- United Shoe Workers of America, 1951 (Box 123, Folder 11)
  - Mobil Oil Corp. -and- Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers, 1966 (Box 123, Folder 12)
- Modern Air Transport, Inc., 1967 - Murray Leather, 7/27/62 (Box 124)
  - Modern Air Transport, Inc. and Air Line Pilots Association International, 1967 (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - Modern Air Transport, Air Line Pilots Association International Council 50, 1966 (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - Modern Leather and Finishing Co. and International Fur and Leather Workers Union -Local 21, 1948 (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - Modern Leather and Finishing Co. Inc. Peabody, Mass. (and) Leather Workers International Union, 1957 (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - Modern Leather Co. Spring St. (and) Leather Workers Org. Committee, 1956 (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - Modern Leather Finishing Co. and Leather Workers International Union, 1960 (Box 124, Folder 6)
  - Modern Leather Co. Peabody, Mass. (and) Leather Workers International Union Local 21, 1960 (Box 124, Folder 7)
  - Modern Leather Company and L.W.I.U. Local 21, 1964 (Box 124, Folder 8)
  - New Bedford Rayon Div. Mohasco Industries, Inc. (and) Textile Workers Union of America Case Bos. L-111-60 L-279-60, 1960 (Box 124, Folder 9)
  - Mohawk Airlines, Inc. and A.L.P.A. Case 5123, 1964 (Box 124, Folder 10)
  - Mohawk Airlines, Inc. and A.L.P.A. 788, 1967 (Box 124, Folder 11)
  - Monomac Spinning Mills United Textile Workers Union of America, 1949 (Box 124, Folder 12)
  - Monomac Spinning Mill Division United Textile Workers of America Local 30, 1948 (Box 124, Folder 13)
  - Monsanto Chemical Company and U.E.R.M.W.A., Local 288 C.I.O., 1947 (Box 124, Folder 14)
  - Monsanto Chemical Company and U.E.R.M.W.A., Local 288 C.I.O., 1950 (Box 124, Folder 15)
  - Monsanto Chemical Company and U.E.R.M.W.A., Local 288 C.I.O., 1950 (Box 124, Folder 16)
  - Monsanto Chemical Company -and- International Chemical Workers' Union, 1951 (Box 124, Folder 17)
  - Monsanto Chemical Company and I.U.E.R.M.W., Local 288 C.I.O., 1952 (Box 124, Folder 18)
  - Monsanto Chemical Company and I.C.W.U. and AFL, Local 57, 1952 (Box 124, Folder 19)
  - Monsanto Chemical Co. -and- International Chemical Workers Un. Local 57 AFL, 1952 (Box 124, Folder 20)
  - Monsanto Chemical Company and International Chemical Workers Un. Local 57 AFL, 1952 (Box 124, Folder 21)
  - Monsanto Chemical Company and International Chemical Workers Un., AFL, 1953 (Box 124, Folder 22)
  - Monsanto Chemical Company(Plastics Div.) -and- IUERMW, Local 288, 1954 (Box 124, Folder 23)
  - Monsanto Chemical Company Everett Mass. And International Chemical Workers Union, 1955 (Box 124, Folder 24)
  - Monsanto Chemical Company Indian Orchard, Mass. -and- International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 288, 1956 (Box 124, Folder 25)
  - Monsanto Chemical Co., 1956 (Box 124, Folder 26)
  - Morris Tanning Company and International Fur and Leather Workers Union Local 21, 1948 (Box 124, Folder 27)
  - Monsanto Chemical Company Springfield, Mass. (and) IUER and M Workers, Local 288, 1956 (Box 124, Folder 28)
  - Monsanto Chemical Company Springfield, Mass. (and) IUER and M Workers, Local 288, 1956 (Box 124, Folder 29)
  - Monsanto Chemical Company Everett, Mass. (and) IUER and M Workers, Local 57 AFL, 1956 (Box 124, Folder 30)
  - Monsanto Chemical Company Everett, Mass. (and) IUER and M Workers, Local 57 AFL, 1956 (Box 124, Folder 31)
  - Murray Leather Company Woburn, Mass. (and) Leather Workers International Union Local 22 and 295, 1958 (Box 124, Folder 32)
  - Murray Leather Company Woburn, Mass. (and) Leather Workers International E. Jennings Discharge, 1958 (Box 124, Folder 33)
  - Murray Leather Company Woburn, Mass. (and) Leather Workers International Union of America Local 22, 1958 (Box 124, Folder 34)
  - Murray Leather Company Woburn, Mass. (and) Leather Workers International Union Local 22, 1958 (Box 124, Folder 35)
  - Murray Leather Company Woburn, Mass. (and) Leather Workers International Union, 1960 (Box 124, Folder 36)
  - Murray Leather, 1962 (Box 124, Folder 37)
  - Murray Leather, 1962 (Box 124, Folder 38)
  - Narragansett Hotel Providence, R.I. and Union, 1957 (Box 124, Folder 39)
- Nauragansett Hotel (Providence), 2/14/57 - National Standard Co., 6/30/64 (Box 125)
  - United Novelty Workers, Local 66 Affiliated with Retail Wholesale and Dept. Store Union, C.I.O. -and- Nashua Plates Co. Inc., 1955 (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - National Airlines System Board of Adjustment Grievance of E. P. McDonald, 1948-1950 (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - National Airlines System Board of Adjustment Grievance of E. P. McDonald, 1948-1950 (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - National Airlines System Board of Adjustment Grievance of E. P. McDonald, 1950 (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - Grievance of E.P. McDonald, 1950 (Box 125, Folder 5)
  - Grievance of E.P. McDonald, 1950 (Box 125, Folder 6)
  - Grievance of E.P. McDonald, 1950 (Box 125, Folder 7)
  - Grievance of E.P. McDonald, 1950 (Box 125, Folder 8)
  - Carrier's Exhibit, 1950 (Box 125, Folder 9)
  - National Airlines, Inc. -and- National Airlines Pilots' System Board Adjustment, 1950 (Box 125, Folder 10)
  - National Standard Co. -Worcester Tire Works -and- United Steelworkers of America, 1948 (Box 125, Folder 11)
  - National Standard Company - Worcester Wire Works -and- United Steelworkers of America, 1949 (Box 125, Folder 12)
  - National Standard Co. -and- United Steelworkers of America., Local 1394, 1953 (Box 125, Folder 13)
  - National Standard Co. -and- United Steelworkers of America, 1953 (Box 125, Folder 14)
  - National Standard Company Niles, Michigan -and- United Steelworkers of America, 1958 (Box 125, Folder 15)
  - National Standard Company Niles, Michigan -and- United Steelworkers of America, 1960 (Box 125, Folder 16)
  - National Glass Co., Inc. (Natcor Div. -and- United Steelworkers of America, CIO, 1954 (Box 125, Folder 17)
  - National Plainfield Corp. -and- United Steelworkers of America, CIO, 1954 (Box 125, Folder 18)
- Neptune Trawling Co., 2/25/52 - City of New York, 9/21/67 (Box 126)
  - Neptune Trawling Company -and- Atlantic Fisherman's Union, 1952 (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - New Britain Machine Company and United Elec. Radio and Machine Workers CIO Local 207, 1947 (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - New Bedford Gas and Edison Light Co. and Bro. Utility Workers of New Eng., Inc., 1952 (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - New Bedford Rayon Company New Bedford Mass. (and) Textile Workers Union of America, 1956 (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - New Bedford Rayon Co. and New Bedford Joint Board, 1965 (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - New Britain Machine, 1954 (Box 126, Folder 6)
  - New Britain Machine Company and I.A.M. Lodge 1021, 1954 (Box 126, Folder 7)
  - New Britain Machine Company and I.A.M., 1954 (Box 126, Folder 8)
  - New Britain Machine Company and I.A.M., 1954 (Box 126, Folder 9)
  - New Britain Machine Company and I.A.M., Lodge 1021, 1955 (Box 126, Folder 10)
  - New Britain Machine Company and I.A.M., 1959 (Box 126, Folder 11)
  - N.E. Alloy Casting Corp. and I.U.E. Amalgamated Local 281, 1964 (Box 126, Folder 12)
  - N.E. Master Textile Engraver Build and Textile Workers of America, 1947 (Box 126, Folder 13)
  - New England Provision Company and United Packinghouse Workers of America CIO, 1949 (Box 126, Folder 14)
  - New England Provision Company, Inc. -and- United Packinghouse Workers of America, 1952 (Box 126, Folder 15)
  - New England Provision Co. and United Packing House Workers., Local 11, 1953 (Box 126, Folder 16)
  - New England Provision Co. and United Packing House Workers., Local 11, 1954 (Box 126, Folder 17)
  - New England Provision Co. and United Packing House Workers., Local 11, 1957 (Box 126, Folder 18)
  - N.E. Wooden Ware Corp. and Int'l. Bro. Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers, 1966 (Box 126, Folder 19)
  - New Jersey Rubber Co. and URCL and PWA Case L-28337 Bost. L-141 60, 1960 (Box 126, Folder 20)
  - New Jersey Rubber Co. and URCL and PWA Case L-32971 Bos. L-225-61, 1962 (Box 126, Folder 21)
  - New London Mills, Inc. and Upp Local 462 L-46986, 1966 (Box 126, Folder 22)
  - Newport Clothing Manufacturing Co. -and- Amalgamated Clothing Workers Union, 1951 (Box 126, Folder 23)
  - N.Y. Air Brake Co. Bif Division and U.S.W.A., 1966 (Box 126, Folder 24)
  - New York Airways, Inc. and A.L.P.A. 6145, 1967 (Box 126, Folder 25)
  - N.Y. Airways and Air Lne. Pil. Assn. Griev., 1962 (Box 126, Folder 26)
  - NY Airways, Inc. and Air Ln. Pil. Assn. Griev. 3506, 1962 (Box 126, Folder 27)
  - NY Airways and Aire Lne. Pil. Assn. Griev. 3508, 1962 (Box 126, Folder 28)
  - NY Airways Inc. and Air Lne. Pil. Assoc. Griev. 3579, 1962 (Box 126, Folder 29)
  - N.Y. Airways Inc. Air Line Pil. Assoc. 3289, 1962 (Box 126, Folder 30)
  - New York city and AFSCME, Local 371, 1967 (Box 126, Folder 31)
  - New York City Dept. of Welfare and Welfare Local No. 1549, 1968 (Box 126, Folder 32)
  - City of New York Welfare Dept. Social Service and Clerical Employees, 1967 (Box 126, Folder 33)
- New York Milk Fund, 2/8/56 - Oxford Paper Co., 3/11/64 (Box 127)
  - New York Milk Fund, 1956 (Box 127, Folder 1)
  - United Papermakers and Paperworkers and New York and Pennsylvania Co. L-35452, 1962 (Box 127, Folder 2)
  - New York Telephone Co. and Communication Workers of America, 1963 (Box 127, Folder 3)
  - Niagara Falls Gazette Publishing Corp. American Newspaper Guild Local 26, 1963 (Box 127, Folder 4)
  - Northeast Airlines and A.L.P.A., 1967 (Box 127, Folder 5)
  - Nicholson File Company -and- United Steelworkers of America - C.I.O., 1951 (Box 127, Folder 6)
  - North Eastern Culvert and International Bro. Teamsters, 1966 (Box 127, Folder 7)
  - Northern Chemical Industries Searsport, Maine (and) International Chemical Wkrs. Union, 1959 (Box 127, Folder 8)
  - Northern Chemical Industries Searsport, Maine (and) International Chemical Wkrs. Union Grievance 25-K, 1959 (Box 127, Folder 9)
  - Northern Chemical Industries Searsport, Maine (and) International Chemical Wkrs. Union Grievance 29-K, 1959 (Box 127, Folder 10)
  - Northern Chemical Industries Searsport, Maine (and) International Chemical Wkrs. Union Local 650 grievance 28-K, 1959 (Box 127, Folder 11)
  - Northern Chemical Industries Searsport, Maine (and) International Chemical Wkrs. Union Local 650, 1960 (Box 127, Folder 12)
  - Northern Steel, 1964 (Box 127, Folder 13)
  - Northwest Airlines, Inc. -and- NWA-IAM System Board of Adjustment, 1954 (Box 127, Folder 14)
  - Northwest Airlines, Inc. -and- NWA-IAM System Board of Adjustment, 1954 (Box 127, Folder 15)
  - Northwest Airlines, Inc. -and- NWA-IAM System Board of Adjustment, 1961 (Box 127, Folder 16)
  - Northwest Airlines, Inc. -and- Transport Workers, Un. Of Am. And Its Air Transport, Local 523 Folder 2, 1961 (Box 127, Folder 17)
  - Northwest Airlines, Inc. and I.A.M. 143 64-8, 1964 (Box 127, Folder 18)
  - Northwest Airlines, Inc. -and- I.A.M., 1966 (Box 127, Folder 19)
  - O.K. Tool Co. and I.A.M., Local 1994, 1953 (Box 127, Folder 20)
  - Oakville Mfg. Co. and U.A.W. 1251 L-39681, 1964 (Box 127, Folder 21)
  - Ocean Spray Cranberries and Teamster, Local 653, 1964 (Box 127, Folder 22)
  - Thomas O'Keefe Leather Co. -and- Local 21, Leather Workers Union, 1955 (Box 127, Folder 23)
  - Old Colony Shoe Company and Brotherhood of Shoe and Allied Craftsmen, 1959 (Box 127, Folder 24)
  - Olin Mathieson Chemical Corp. 275 Winchester Ave. N.H. Conn. I.A.M. Grievance 2505 Report-in-[ay, 1957 (Box 127, Folder 25)
  - Olin Mathieson Chemical Corp. and I.A.M. Lodge 609, 1969 (Box 127, Folder 26)
  - Olson Manfg. Co. Worcester Mass. (and) United Steelworkers of America Case L-21805 L-75-58, 1958 (Box 127, Folder 27)